so after my last comment on that 69
should have had a different app of
course that's where my brain wind
because sometimes it goes there and I
think although many of these I actually
think a lot of Internet spaces one of
the things that's my pet peeve and I
maybe I need to look into your ears too
why that is but one of the reasons I
don't like a lot of the stuff that's out
there is the misogyny and the patriarchy
this out there turned all of them and
just unsafe sex the sex turban spaces
where men feel it's their right to send
you dick pics and you have it it's just
ends up being almost violent and I don't
like it but this one people make facts
about it one of the things I do like
this isn't my idea but I do think it
needs you need to find a way to implant
it's something similar on any site where
you have crowdsourcing its periscope
which is a live streaming site if you
don't know it and I love the technology
I love that you can live stream and have
people comment and I mean like anything
that's online but whenever you watch a
woman well the women I've watched doing
it there's always people that comment
like take off your shirt like just I
need appropriate sexual comment and
sometimes it's very obvious not very
obvious more indicated that that's
welcome to the person speaking based on
how she reacts based on her demeanor and
it just if you're talking about finance
clearly not if you are wearing a low-cut
top and positioning the camera on that
may be so he's so happy and knowing that
so so when there is an offensive comment
so just like in anything if someone says
that it's offensive it then pops up in a
bunch of the people watching the screens
and that like is this offensive so its
crowdsourcing in the policing which I
love and I think that needs to be done
more I think that Facebook with its
banning of breastfeeding
it's like someone tags it for nudity's
and when it could be like okay is this
the fort what forms of nudity that are
allowed
here or if you wanted more of an
algorithm type but still crowdsourcing
cuz it need to come up and ask you that
or more of like YouTube where they've
started non-monetary only could have
known if they've ever monetized sites
that they raid um
channels that they were whatever the
listing on his YouTube channel stopped
an episode on the YouTube we like an an
upload once it's been flagged as like
mature content and they don't get they
don't get much money on it cuz there's
no advertising and there's a lot of
things that are mature context that
shouldn't be mature content like is this
LGBT related and not like if it was an
LGBT related would it still need to be a
to be mature content cuz if you know
talking about blowjobs in one way and
then talking about blowjobs in the other
way is if you're talking about feeling
safe in your own skin that's something
thirteen-year-old should have access to
and people creating that content should
have just as much means to make the
money on it as anyone else as people you
know giving makeup tips or power jitan
so I think a crowd-sourced policing Pro
online policing program is very
important in in all of these aspects so
that is Apple number 70